Wow...
It looks like snow!
Awesome!
Ooh...
Looks like the cherry blossoms have reached their end for this year.
Really?!
Ah! Tomorrow is a holiday, so let's all go flower viewing!
Um...
That sounds like fun!
Shall we make lunches to bring with us?
Um...
Ah! I'll make some too!
Hey, c'mon now...
That sounds great!
Yay!
Hey...
Ah, I'm sorry... I went off and decided on my own.
Ah, don't worry about it... I'm fine with it.
I'll bring something as well.
Thank you.
Kouki's always causing you trouble too...
Is that so? Sorry...
Kouki! Rin-chan!
We'll meet tomorrow at 8:00, in the park!
Okay!
That's early!
Fine, 9:00 then!
You're supposed to view flowers in the afternoon.
Okay, then 10:00...
Oh, I have to watch Grand Sazer...
Guess it'll have to be afternoon after all!
Daikichi!
Where do we keep the water bottles?
Below the sink, right?
Ah, that's right.
It may rain tomorrow.
Huh?!
A "spring storm", they're saying.
A storm...
Ah! It's raining already!
Holy crap... It's really coming down.
Let's make teru teru bouzu!
Daikichi!
The rain's stopped!
Ooh, we did it.
The teru teru bouzu saved the day!
Am I dressed a bit too drab?
I can smell the greenery!
All the flowers are gone!
Hey!
Kouki-kun!
Wow!
Daikichi!
The sky's in full bloom!
「Sky in Full Bloom」